Drew K Goodin

dkg@fastmail.com | 214.288.6399 | SF Bay Area | https://goodind1.github.io

EDUCATION

PURDUE UNIVERSITY I BS MATHEMATICS

West Lafayette, IN

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Multi-faceted professional with experience from carpentry to database administration now moving head-on toward high school education and coaching. Deep mathematical and computational knowledge, and enthusiam for bridging the two. Intent to pursue MS degree within the next three years.

WORK FXPFRIFNCE

DREW GOODIN GUITAR CABINETRY | Owner / Builder

Hayward, CA | November 2015 - Present

- Builder of high end speaker enclosures for guitar amplifiers
- · Work with vendors, suppliers, and customers daily to deliver my product
- · All web development / server admin, marketing and social media

VIGILENT INC | Technical Support Engineer Oakland, CA / Remote | March 2020 - November 2020

- · Support the deployment and use of very technical AI-based software related to buillding automation and cooling
- First line of response for JIRA tickets and customer phone calls
- · Provide and document solutions directly or triage to engineering
- Develop internal tools for engineering productivity, infrastructure, and documentation
- Manage internal test Virtual Machines (VMWare / Ubuntu)
- Run remote upgrades of customer systems via SCP / SSH sessions

PALO ALTO MEDICAL FOUNDATION | HRIS SPECIALIST Mountain View, CA / Burlingame, CA | March 2012 - November 2015

- Develop database queries, both GUI-based and raw SQL, for the purpose of HR data reports and analysis
- Ensure integrity and data standard compliance of all edits and new entries to personnel data across 7000+ employees and several physical sites
- · Serve as Help Desk for all HR related information systems including timekeeping (Kronos) and HRMS (Lawson)

MATHEMATICS / TEACHING INTERESTS

POTENTIAL COURSES TAUGHT (HIGH COMPETENCE) HIGHER ACADEMIC INTERESTS PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Algebra I / II, Precalculus, AP Calculus Real Analysis, Functional Analysis Perl, SQL

OTHER EMPLOYMENT

HALF MOON BAY GOLF LINKS, 2011-18, SEASONAL

Assistant golf professional / golf shop associate. Involved in all aspects of guest experience; sales, reservations, tournament organization.

CARPENTER / APPRENTICE, 2016 - PRES, VARIOUS LOCATIONS

References available. Worked as a deck builder / landscape carpenter in Dallas from 2016-17 as well as high-end shop woodwork in the Bay Area from 2018-21.